Jason Chu

Digital Marketing Manager - R2integrated

San Francisco, CA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Jason-Chu/a2b6069947e5e4de

I have more than two years of experiences planning and managing digital ads campaigns (i.e. facebook and adwords) and gaining real results from my campaigns to dramatically reduce the company's user acquisition cost and gain measurable and significant traffic volumes to the landing pages as well as specific web pages. Love to use google analytics in order to find opportunities for massive audience appeal.

I was previously a software engineer, now switching to digital marketing as I find out that I am more passionate in this field with better fit in my skills set.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Marketing Manager

R2integrated - May 2016 to Present

Help their clients with SEO, content marketing, plan and create SEM campaigns, mostly on adwords. My effort help them generating high quality leads with greater ROI and conversion.

SEO & SEM specialist

Lupeer - February 2015 to January 2016

Managing both paid and organic traffic campaigns, mostly through facebook and google.

Software Engineer

PayPal - August 2013 to November 2014

In PayPal I focused primary on developing and analyzing relational databases, and also learned to use a variety of tools to test usability and performance of the mobile site like A/B testing, paper prototype testing, and hallway testing.

Software Engineering Intern

Airbnb - January 2012 to March 2012

Use clean javascript codes with airbnb"s own frontend framework to assist updating frontend functionalities and develop new features with team.

Calculus Tutor

Varsity Tutors - May 2011 to December 2011

online math tutor for all kinds of people with different careers and educational background

Research And Teaching Assistant at University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign

Assist Computer Science professor

- March 2010 to June 2010

to create learning materials and grade exams for two classes.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Computer Science & Economics

University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign - Urbana-Champaign, IL 2011 to 2015